JOJO'S BIZARRE ADVENTURE
DIAMOND IS UNBREAKABLE
These faceless gazes pass by one another
A wound to the heart changes our everyday
Encounters without boundaries
The bizarre is our normal U-yeh
These ordinary mornings,
we're laughing on the surface
Mysteries drawn to each other,
identity still unknown
Without a heads up,
it's quietly lurking somewhere in this town
Although we bicker and complain
In the end, we celebrate
Dancing through the everyday
Crazy Noisy Bizarre Town
EPISODE 3
THE NIJIMURA BROTHERS, PART 1
MORIOH MUNICIPAL RECORDS
KIDNAPPINGS AND ABDUCTIONS
HAVE YOU SEEN THIS PERSON?
BILLION
MORIOH LANDMARK 1
ANGELO'S ROCK
ONE MINUTE WALK FROM
MORIOH JOZENJI STREET BUS STOP #3.
ANGELO'S ROCK: TOWN LANDMARK AND
HOT-SPOT FOR ROMANTIC RENDEZVOUS.
FOR YEARS IT'S CHARMED
THE RESIDENTS OF MORIOH,
DESPITE ITS SLIGHTLY
DISTURBING APPEARANCE.
NO TRESPASSING
NO __ PASSING
EPISODE 4
THE NIJIMURA BROTHERS, PART 2